is with us
for some thoughts on the market there's
14 minutes to go for clothes amarish
any thoughts on lombard which yash was
just detailing
good afternoon
i think like i've been saying earlier
also that i think this year should be
the year for the insurance companies
both uh live fishers as well as general
and uh lombard in fact uh falls in that
uh i mean basically because we have seen
huge amount of claims in the last two
years because of covet and post that we
have seen premiums also rising at the
same time going ahead i think the claims
will be lower so you'll have the benefit
of
higher premiums and lower claims over
the next couple of quarters i think that
should play off well for the insurance
companies so at these levels i think
it's a good time to pick up across
all right uh
and uh what are your thoughts on uh a
couple of these cement stocks ambrish
you know because we have seen a fair
amount of correction on them ever since
ultratech announced their capex but over
the last two trading sessions we are
seeing some bit of a bounce back say
something like a ramco has moved to the
high point jk cement 2 has recovered
fair bit in fact it's now almost erased
all the losses that it saw in the first
three trading sessions of this week
i see america uh like a capex by someone
as large as ultra tech should not be
taken negatively but the markets took it
negatively i mean that clearly showed
that the amount of confidence it is
there the sector the sort of a growth
which can be seen in the sector over the
next couple of years at the same time we
should remember that a capex takes at
least about 24 months to 30 months for
uh i mean that the quantity to
in fact come into the market so
i mean one need not be worried that uh
just i mean in the next couple of months
you'll have uh
i mean uh the total capacity going up so
much so
clearly uh i mean if you're looking at
the sort of infra development which is
happening the real sector the way it's
growing
uh cement demand is surely going to
increase much faster than the gdp growth
which is looking at so uh i mean i think
one should still be quite positive on
cement and
this increase in capex clearly i mean i
would look at it positively
uh okay uh we should look at it
positively stocks though still
i mean you know hint some glimmer of
pullbacks but i mean not really uh very
much there uh any thoughts on names like
taurus et cetera ambrish i mean it's
seen a big four percent crack today
right
uh in fact uh steel and metals overall
has been a sector where i've been a bit
sort of a cautious to negative for the
last couple of months and i've said that
the best of it is already behind they
have peaked off so even at these levels
i would say it's time to exit the steel
as well as aluminum stocks because i
think the prices are peaked out and
that's the way it's going to be at least
for that i mean
a forcible couple of quarters so the
best is behind them they have shown the
best of profits in the last three
quarters i don't think going ahead the
next at least three to four quarters
you'll see what we've seen in the last
two three quarters
right amrish stay on we are seeing uh
some moves in a couple of names tomato
after a big decline yesterday is
bouncing back once again it's in fact uh
recovered almost six percent from
today's low currently sitting around
that 69 rupee per share mark the other
stock which is doing well is avenue
supermarkets as well which has moved to
the high point of trade from uh low in
today's trading session it's recovered
almost four and a half odd percent still
a fair bit away from its uh all-time
high almost 35-40 percent away ah hang
in there i'm rich we take a short break
come back tell you more about the
markets as well as individual stocks
[Music]
you